Guide to the Lin Carter Papers, 1900s-2001 and undated RL.11079
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Writings, 1900s-1990 and undated; 1
  - Carter's Writings, 1
    - Kellory the Warlock, 1956 Apr., 1984, and undated; 5 folders (Box 3)
      typescript with note "original manuscript" (undated, 04/28/1956); typescript with handwritten notes, incomplete (undated, incl. pp. 1-39 with I) "Dark Palace of the Flame" and II) beginning of "In the Valley of Silence", pp. 80-224 with III) "The City Where Death Was King," IV) "Shadows in the Dark," V) "The Smile of the Face of the Beast," VI) "Lord of the Shadows," VII) "The Gray Enchanter"); typescript with handwritten notes, part II: "In the Valley of Silence" (undated); setting copy with handwritten notes (09/1984); galley proofs with handwritten notes (10-11/1984)
    - Keru, undated (Box 3)
    - Kesrick, undated; 2 folders (Box 3)
      various notes, typescript with handwritten notes incl. chapters I and II (pp. 1-10, incomplete), typescript with handwritten notes inc. entire novel
    - Khymyrium, 1972 Nov.; 3 folders (Box 3)
      various handwritten and typed notes, synopses of "The First Part: Lords of the Morning. Book OneThe Lion of Memnos" and "Book Two: The Eight Cities" (undated), two drafts of the chapter "The Tourney" (undated, one with note "final draft"); typescript titled "Chapter One: Azlon" (undated, incomplete, incl. pp. 1-61, sections 1-13); typescript "Notes: On the Making of Khymyrium" with some handwritten notes, incl. the note "Only original manuscript. November 1972"
    - Khyrium, undated (Box 3)
      various handwritten notes
    - King of the World's Edge, undated (Box 3)
      typescript with handwritten notes (incomplete, contains pp. 1-86 "I. A Shadow Cast," "II. The Battle Joint," and title page of "III. An Oath Remembered"
    - The Kingdom Next Door, undated (Box 3)
      notes, typescript of "Chapter 1. The Door That Wasn't There," manuscript of "1. Angelica's Adventure," various single typed pages with parts of the two chapters
    - Kingdoms of Sorcery, 1972 (Box 3)
      single typscript page with acknowledgements
    - The Kuttner Mythos, undated (Box 3)
      includes copies of the the stories "The Watcher at the Door. A Brief, Shuddery Story About the Horror That Haunted Keene's 'dreams (sic)" by Henry Kuttner, "The Hunt. Iod, Merciless Scourge of Damned Souls, Pays an Earthly Visit!" by Henry Kuttner, and "The Invaders. When Furies of Hell From Another Age are Loosed Upon Eearth by Michael Hayward, They Teach Him a Nobler Wisdom!" by Keith Hammond
    - Kyrith notes, undated (Box 3)
      notes and and brief manuscripts
    - The Laughter of Han, 1979 Feb. 17 (Box 3)
      typescript with handwritten notes, incl. note "Only original mansucript of this Simrana Tale, whose second and final version was written on 17 February 1979"
    - The Lemurian Chronicles, undated (Box 3)
      notes and sketch, two typescripts (one with handwritten notes) of "The First Book: The Children of Serpent," typescripts with handwritten notes of "The Second Book: The Thousand Year War," "The Nine Cities," "The Fourth Book: The Wars of Thongor the Mighty," "The Fifth Book: The Golden Empire of the Sun," "From the Lemurian Chronicles"
    - A Letter to Judith. A Work of Poetry by Lin Carter, 1959 Apr.-May (Box 3)
      four prints
    - Life of Eibon According to Cyron of Varaad, undated; 2 folders (Box 3)
      notes, manuscript with note "first draft begun Oct 9, 10," half type-/manuscript version (undated), single typescript pages (undated), typescript version (undated)
    - Lohengrin in the Venusberg, 1986 May 10 (Box 9)
    - Lohengrin in the Venusberg, 1986 May (Box 3)
      typescript with handwritten notes and attached note "final version, completed 10 May, 1986," single typescript pages with different versions
    - (Lord Dunsany:) Editor's Note by Carter, undated (Box 3)
      typescript of Carter's editor's note from unidentified publication
    - Lost Nonsense by Lewis Carroll and Edward Lear. Collected, with an Introduction and Notes, by Lin Carter (to which has been added, as a sort of Postscript, a Morsel of Andrew Lang), undated (Box 3)
    - Lost Races, Forgotten Cities, 1975 Jan. (Box 3)
      typescript with handwritten notes, incl. "Only original manuscript copy of this article, written 21 January 1975." Originally included in one folder with "The High History of Sinbad the Sailor" and "About the Slayer of Souls and Robert W. Chambers: Lord of the Black Throne" with the attached note "For Amra or Amazing."
    - The Magical Kingdom of Yoom, 1954 Feb. (Box 3)
      sketches, typescript with handwritten notes, incl. note "Second Draft: 32,532 words, completed 27 Feb '54"
    - More Limmericks from Yuggoth, undated (Box 9)
    - Murder in Space, undated (Box 3)
    - Mythos Data, 1983 and undated (Box 3)
      notes, clipped articles (incl. "The Thing in the Moonlight" by H. P. Lovecraft and Brian Lumley), correspondence re Carter's collection of Clark Ashton Smith works dated in 1983
    - The Near Stars, undated (Box 9)
      Notes, story drafts
    - Necronomicon: Book I,ii: The Thing Under Memphis from the Necronomicon, undated (Box 3)
    - Necronomicon: Book II, The Book of Preparations, undated (Box 3)
    - Necronomicon: Book III, The Book of Gates, undated (Box 3)
    - Necronomicon: Book IV, The Book of Dismissals, undated (Box 3)
    - Necronomicon: The City of Pillars. From the Necronomicon of Abdul Alhazred, undated (Box 3)
      typescript with some handwritten notes, incl. a page titled "Note to 'The City of Pillars'"
    - Necronomicon: The Fourth Narrative From the Necronomicon, called The Vault Beneath the Mosque from the John Dee Translation, edited and modernized by Lin Carter, undated (Box 3)
    - Necronomicon: The Fifth Narrative From the Necronomicon, called Dreams of the Black Lotus from the John Dee Translation, as edited and modernized by Lin Carter, with notes, undated (Box 3)
    - Necronomicon: The Fifth Narrative From the Necronomicon, called MNOMQUAH from the John Dee Translation, as edited by Lin Carter, undated (Box 3)
    - Necronomicon: The Eighth Narrative From the Necronomicon, called The Madness Out of Time from the John Dee Translation, as edited and modernized by Lin Carter, undated (Box 4)
      typescript with handwritten notes, incl. "Only original manuscript of this 8th narrative from the Necronomicon, completed on 30 January 1986;" "Work-Notes for Madness Out of Time"
    - Necronomicon: The Ninth Narrative From the Necronomicon, called The Shadow From the Stars from the John Dee Translation, as edited and modernized by Lin Carter, with notes, undated (Box 4)
      typescript with handwritten ntoes
    - Necronomicon: Pages From 1622 Wormius Necronomicon, undated (Box 4)
      incl. handwritten notes, typescripts of "Translator's Note" by Carter," "Acolyte of the Flame From the Pnakotic Manuscripts," and others (incomplete)
    - Necronomicon: Them From Outside. A Narrative From the Necronomicon, undated (Box 4)
    - Necronomicon: notes, undated (Box 4)
      typescript notes
    - Neomythology. An Introduction, 1976 Jan. 17 and undated (Box 4)
      typescript with some handwritten notes, incl. "copy of the text of the published version, as edited by de Camp," typescript with handwritten notes, incl. "only existing manuscript copy of the original version of this introductory essay, including the manuscript of 'Quixote With a Pen.' 17 January 1976."
    - Neo-Witchcraft, undated (Box 4)
    - New Mythos Tales, undated (Box 4)
      typescripts of poems "To Lord Dunsany," "The Elf-King's Castle," "Limericks From Yuggoth"
    - No Joy in Mudville, undated (Box 4)
      typescript with some handwritten notes, notes
    - Novels of Adult Fantasy, undated (Box 4)
      typescript with introduction by Carter and clipping
    - Of Hobbits, Heroes, and Ego-Boo, 1973 Feb. (Box 4)
      typescript with handwritten notes, incl. note "Completed Feb. 1973. Only original copy."
    - The Offspring, undated (Box 4)
      typescript with handwritten notes, manuscript titled "The Red Offering"
    - One Dragon Too Many. Being: A True and Exact Narration From the Annales Puffleburgensis. Newly Edited and Annotated, undated (Box 4)
      copy of print
    - Outlaws of the Vortex, undated (Box 4)
    - Partholon, undated; 2 folders (Box 9)
      Typescript, map
    - Partholon, undated (Box 4)
      typescript with handwritten ntoes titled "Notes for 'Partholon'"
    - Perchance to Dream, undated (Box 4)
    - The Pilfered Porcelain, undated (Box 4)
    - The Pink Dragon of Oz, undated (Box 4)
      typescripts with handwritten notes, incl. attached note "sample chapters of 'The Pink Dragon of Oz'", incl. "Betsy Puts on Her High Hat" and "A Nonwelcome to Non"
    - Pirates and Monsters, undated (Box 4)
      typescripts with handwritten notes
    - Planet in Peril, Star Pirate battles the murder monsters of Mercury in, undated (Box 4)
    - Pnakotic Fragments, undated (Box 4)
      incl. manuscript of "Introduction," manuscript of "The Stairs in the Crypt," typescript with handwritten notes titled "Acolyte of the Flame From the Pnakotic Manuscripts" (with "Translator's Note" by Carter), manuscript of "Unkown Kadath," untitled typescript with handwritten notes, outline of Charnel House Chapbooks editor Robert M. Price, various notes
    - Poems, 1951-1956, 1958 and undated; 8 folders (Box 4)
      typescripts (partly with handwritten notes) and manuscripts
    - Poetry drafts, misc., 1974 and undated (Box 9)
      Includes a napkin with a poem about farts.
    - Prince Tallador, undated (Box 4)
      typesrcipts of "The Perilous Voyage of The Silver Bough, and of how The Young Prince Came at Last Unto the Kingdom of Faerie," "Of How Prince Tallador Sought The Silver Apples of the Moon And of That Which Befell Him" (incomplete, with handwritten notes), and incomplete, untitled typescript (missing pp. 1-2, 6, 21ff.); notes
    - Prince Vathek, 1986 May 13 (Box 9)
    - Prince Vathek, 1986 May 13 and undated (Box 4)
      drafts and fragments, incl. "First Rough Draft," "Final Version completed 13 May, 1986," "Towards the Final Version"
    - Prince Vathek/Lohengrin, undated (Box 4)
      typescript with handwritten notes (incomplete, missing pp. 20ff.) with attached note "Version of 'Prince Vathek' which was turned into draft of 'Lohengrin'"
    - Psychocosmos. A Dream, 1948-1955 (Box 4)
      typescripts with handwritten notes of drafts II, III, IV, and V (drafts IV and V with the title "Fantasmagoria"); with notes on dates "1st Draft: 174 L. (Jan-Mar '48), 2nd Draft: 192 L. (Apr - May '48), 3rd Draft: 228 L. (early 1949-'50), 4th Draft: 348 L. (completed 2 Oct '53)"
    - Puffleburg Tales, undated (Box 9)
    - Rogan's Way, undated (Box 9)
    - Saint Hilarion, undated (Box 9)
    - The Secret History, undated (Box 4)
      typescript and handwritten notes, incl. two versions of "Unknown Civilizations: Two Million Years of Man's Suppressed History, (by) Brian Sorley," "The Untold Story of Mankind," and "The Mystery Civilization of Gondwane"; newspaper clippings and "Geological Time Chart"
    - Serendippo Notes, undated (Box 4)
      various typed and handwritten notes
    - A Sherlock of the Supernatural, 1975 July 17 (Box 4)
      typescript with handwritten notes, incl. note "Only existing copy of this introduction to ("The Adventures of Jules de Grandin" by Quinn). Written in its entirety on 17 July 1975."
    - Shoulder the Sky, 1987 Sept. 4 (Box 4)
    - The Slayer of Dragons. The Seven Deeds of Rustum, Hero of Persia, undated (Box 4)
      incl. typescript of "A Note From the Author" and "Chapter One: The Crowning of Kaikooz," typescript of "Synopsis of the remainder of Slayer-of-Dragons"; typescript of "Chapter One: The Crowning of Kaikooz" under the title "Shah Namah: The Book of Kings and Heroes - A New Version"; typescript with handwritten notes incl. the chapters "The Crowning of Kaikooz," "The Anger of Zal," "The Arming of Rustum," "The Courage of Rustum," "The Whelming of Suffid"
    - The Slither From the Slime, 1958 Sept. (Box 4)
      xerox copy from "Inside SF," no. 53, September 1958
    - The Slitherer From the Slime, undated (Box 4)
    - The Snout in the Dark, undated (Box 4)
      typescript with synopsis
    - Something in the Moonlight, undated (Box 4)
    - Son of Cthulhu, 1991 and undated; 2 folders (Box 9)
      Draft and copyright registration by Robert Price
    - The Stairs in the Crypt. From the Pnakotic Manuscripts, undated (Box 4)
    - The Strange Doom of Enos Harker, undated (Box 4)
      typescript with handwritten with "Statement of Paxton Blaine" and typescript with attached note "new and improved continuation of The Lin Carter fragment 'The Strange Doom of Enos Harker' (for The Xothic Legend Cycle)"
    - Strange Manuscript Found in the Vermont Woods, undated (Box 4)
    - Summer Magic, undated (Box 4)
      typescript with handwritten notes, incl. stories on Phil (chapters "1. The Nearsighted Knight," "2. The Fairy of the Mountain," "3. The Palace Beneath the Lake," "5. (sic) To the Far Antipodes," "6. The Damsel in Distress," "7. Rescuing Heroldine," "8. The Picnic on Pittipoo," "9. Off to Horoscopia!", "10. The Absent-Minded Astrologer," "11. El Cheiro Predicts," "12. The Interrupted Invasion," "13. Hedzoff Takes Command," "14. One Invasion, On the Rocks'" "15. Hail to the Visctors!", "About the Author (Lin Carter));" typescript with handwritten notes, incl. stories on Peter and Betsy (chapters "1. Orphans!", "2. The Mystery Man," "3. The Expedition," "4. Waiting and Watching," "5. The Third Floor," "6. The Quest is Begun!", "7. Knight vs. Dragon," "8. The Second Adventure," "9. The Giant Who Ned Needeed Glasses (sic)," "10. "Whale Stew," "11. The Locked Door")
    - Susran, undated (Box 4)
      typescript with some handwritten notes, incl. note "for yr Smith issue no. 2"
    - A Swordsman of Mars. The Adventures of Thad Dexter on the Red Planet, undated (Box 4)
      typescript with handwritten notes; also includes typescript with handwritten notes of "Chapter 3. Kar Havas, Panthan" and typescript with handwritten notes of a "Synopsis" of a Mars series
    - The Swordsman of Mars, undated (Box 4)
      manuscript, incl. various other notes ("Mystery of Mars" et al.)
    - Tales From Dickens Pub, undated (Box 4)
    - Tales of Antillia, undated (Box 9)
    - Tara short stories, undated (Box 4)
      typescript with handwritten notes of "Pale Shadow" and typescript with handwritten notes of "The Love of the Sea"
    - Temple of the Flame/The Black Temple, undated (Box 4)
    - Testaments of Carnamagos, Fragments of, undated (Box 4)
    - A Thanatorian Arthopode, undated (Box 4)
      sketch titled "a Thanatorian ARTHOPODE segmented exoskeleton of horny chitin
    - The Theft of the Inimitable, undated (Box 4)
    - The Thievery of Yish, 1981 Jan. 22 and undated (Box 4)
      typescript with some handwritten notes and manuscript with note "Written in its entirety the night of Jan. 22 '81."
    - The Triumph of Malygris, undated; ` (Box 5)
      handwritten notes and various manuscript fragments
    - Thongor, undated (Box 4)
      notes and drafts, incl. several synopses of Thongor stories
    - Thongor (nineteen-years old), undated (Box 4)
      typescript of Thongor story "less than six years before the beginning opening scene of 'Thongor and the Wizard of Lemuria'" starting with chapter 1 "The Sign of the Skull"
    - Thongor stories, undated (Box 4)
      incl. typescript with handwrittten notes of a synopsis of "Thongor Conquers the Underground World," typescript titled "Book 3 - The Warrior of Lemuria. Thongor of Lemuria," typescript titled "Tharth, Son of Thongor"
    - Thongor and the Dragon City, 1970 (Box 11)
      Berkley Medallion paperback edition
    - Thongor the Mighty in Black Moonlight, 1972 July (Box 4)
    - Thongor: The Wizard of Lemuria, undated (Box 4)
      typescript (pages 19, 38, 39 missing)
    - Thongoriana, undated (Box 4)
      notes and various typescript fragments ("The Serpent God/Monster-God of Mommur," "The Secret History of Lemuria," "A Glossary of Lemurian Words and Phrases")
    - Tower at the Edge of Time, 1968-1969, 1999 (Box 12)
    - Unknown Worlds, undated (Box 5)
      typescripts with handwritten notes (incl. "Introduction," "The Worm that Gnaws in the Night," et al.)
    - The Vaults of Yoh-Vombis, undated; 3 folders (Box 5)
      typescripts with handwritten notes titled "From the Vaults of Yoh-Vombis" (incl. "Strange but True," no. 1-5 (untitled), "Materials Towards a Theory That Coincidence is Either a Powerful Force of Nature, Hitherto Unrecognized As Such, or the Interactions With Human History of a Mischievous and Demiurgic Intelligence of Superhuman Power (no. 6)," "Great Smith (no. 8)," "Hors d'Oeuvres (no. 9)," "Notes Towards a Natural History of Trolls," "Unnatural History," "More Giants," "Names to Conjure With"); manuscripts with tables of contents of books I to V
    - The Vengeance of Yig, 1980 Feb. 16 (Box 5)
      typescript with handwritten notes, incl. note "Only existing manuscript of this Cthulhu Mythos story, written in its entirety on 16 February 1980."
    - Visions for Yaddith, undated (Box 5)
      notes and manuscripts (incl. "Introduction," "Cockaigne: Imitations of Immortality," "Galleons of Dream," et al.)
    - A Voyage to Blefuscu, undated (Box 9)
      Typescript draft
    - The Voyage to Blefuscu, by Clefdrig Reldresal, Late Secretary to the Court of Lilliput, translated by Lin Carter, 1986 July 5 (Box 5)
      typescript with handwritten notes, handwritten notes
    - Weird Tales, 1979-1988 and undated; 2 folders (Box 5)
      Folder 1: memoranda of agreements between publisher and ed. Carter, correspondence re "Weird Tales" (to and by Carter) letter templates for contributors and submission guidelines, notice of discontinuation of "Weird Tales," lists of published works in the issues "Weird Tales," various additional material added to the folder by Carter (incl. article by Don Hutchinson, incomplete xerox copy of "Weird Story Reprint: Passing a God" by Henry S. Whitehead, incomplete xerox copy of "The Eyrie" (no author), issue of "The Chicago Fantasy Newsletter" (Vol. III, no. 2/3, Oct. 1980-Jan. 1981, no. 12/13), etc., various handwritten notes; Folder 2: logos and layout templates, cover proofs, typescript with handwritten notes of introduction to "Weird Tales" issue and collection of press quotes on the return of the magazine, typescript with handwritten notes of "Reviewed by Lin Carter" ("Weird Tales," Spring issue 1988)
    - What Goes Up, undated (Box 9)
    - The Winning Cards, 1978 Feb. 11 (Box 5)
      typescript with handwritten notes, incl. "Only original manuscript of this tale, written at a sitting on February 11, 1978."; undated typescript with different version and handwritten notes
    - Wizard of Oz, undated; 2 folders (Box 5)
      Folder 1: typescript with handwritten notes of "The Awful Ogre of Ogodown" (undated earlier, shorter version); Folder 2: complete typescript with handwritten notes without main title (undated later, longer version of "The Awful Ogre of Ogodown, an Oz story"), incl. the chapters "Flying Magici" (ch. 1), "Through the Purple Forest" (ch. 2), "Jandy Finds a Fraidy Cat" (ch. 3), "Dismal Doings in Ogodown" (ch. 4), "Bringing Ogwog Down to Size" (ch. 5), "Dorothy Plans a Visit" (ch. 6), "Watch Out for the Wild Flowers" (ch. 7), "The Owful Ogre Again" (ch. 8), "They Take the High Way" (ch. 9), "Welcome to Tip Top Town" (ch. 10), "Advice From a Looking Glass" (ch. 11), "A Happy Landing" (ch. 12), "Jandy Uses the Strong Box" (ch. 13), "The Hoppers and the Horners" (ch. 14), "A Brief Visit to Cross Town" (ch. 15), "A Meeting at Pop Corners" (ch. 16), "The Helpful Handy Man" (ch. 17), "Fraidy Finds a Friend" (ch. 18), "Meeting Her Mudjesty" (ch. 19), "No Joy in Mudville" (ch. 20), "Crossing Rubber River" (ch. 21), "Why Not Take the Footbridge?" (ch. 22), "Merry Meetings in the Emerald City" (ch. 23). -- Folder 3: typescript with handwritten notes of "High Times on Tip Top Mountain, an Oz story" (incl. the chapters "The Awful Ogre Again;" "They Take the High Way," "Welcome to Tip Top Town," "Advice From a Looking Glass," "); Folder 4: typescript with handwritten notes of "The Wooden Soldier of Oz"; Folder 5: various newspaper and article clippings and other thematically related materials (incl. programs and tickets for several stage productions, and business and member card of the "International Wizard of Oz Club"); typescript of "The Wonderful Land of Oz" by L. Frank Baum, handwritten and typescript notes on "Queen Zixi of IX," "The Laughing Dragon of Oz," "The Wizard of Oz," "Dorothy and the Wizard of Oz," "The Road to Oz" and "Ozma of Oz" by L. Frank Baum; typescript of "A Brief Outline of Oz History Up to and Including Events Early in the Reign of 'The Great Wizard'" by Fred Meyer; typescripts of "The Geography of Oz," "The Tin Woodman and the Tin Soldier of Oz," and "Glinda and the Red Jinn" by Robert R. Pattrick; typescript of "Follow the Yellow Brick Road" by Redd Boggs; typescript of "The Enchanted Tree of Oz. An Unfinished Story by Ruth Plumly Thompson"
    - The Wizard of Vandalex, undated (Box 9)
      Typescripts
    - Wizard's Warrior, undated (Box 9)
    - Wizard's Warrior, undated (Box 5)
    - Xothic Legend Cycle (Cthulhu Mythos), undated (Box 5)
      typescript of "The Dweller in the Tomb," first page of typescript of "The Thing in the Pit," typescript with "Background Notes on the Ythogtha Tales," typescript with handwritten notes incl. table of contents, "Author's Note," and "Introductory Note," some single type- and manuscript pages
    - Yoh-Vambis I, undated (Box 9)
    - Zanthodon: Further Adventures in the Underground World, 1980 (Box 12)
    - Zarkon, Lord of the Unknown, in The Moon Menace. A Case from the Files of Omega, as told to Lin Carter, undated (Box 5)
      typescript with handwritten notes (incl. two versions of a synopsis, chapters 1-3), handwritten notes, and typescript fragments
    - Cover Proofs, undated (Box 5)
      various cover proofs of books written or edited by Carter
    - Abandoned novels, undated (Box 9)
  - Unidentified Writings (likely by Carter), 2
    - The Canticles, undated (Box 5)
    - Conan the Barbarian, 1977 Apr. 24 (Box 5)
      incomplete typescript (p. 1) signed by "LSdeC"
    - The Curious Curse of Grandma's Cottage, undated (Box 5)
      typescript with handwritten notes, incl. chapters "1. Stormy Wheather," "2. All at Sea," "3. Pat Catches a Fish," "4. 'Thar She Blows!'", "5. Dickie Moe," "6. The Ice Island," "7. Igluk of the Ice," "8. Aground!", "9. The Desert Island," "10. Cap'n Brassbottom's Story," "11. On Spyglass Hill"
    - Do you know the great stinkers of history? (quiz), undated (Box 5)
    - The God Augustus, undated (Box 5)
      incomplete typescript (pp. 1-8)
    - How Aladdin Went Down Into the Cave of Treasure and Brought Up the Wonderful Lamp, undated (Box 5)
    - Jungle Boy (from "Chunda of the Lost Continent"), undated (Box 5)
    - A Knife in the Back, undated (Box 5)
    - Lord of the Black Throne, 1977 Sept. 21 (Box 5)
      typescript signed by "LSdeC"
    - The Mystic Council Summons You, undated (Box 5)
    - In Nowhere Street, undated (Box 5)
    - Rebel Priestess/Plenum Agent, undated (Box 5)
      typescript with handwritten notes incl. part "I. Rebell Priestess" and part "II. Plenum Agent" (pp. 4-31) and "Synopsis"; typescript with handwritten notes incl. single pages of different, incomplete version of part "I. Rebel Priestess" (pp. 4, -6, 9, 18-24)
    - The Sawhorse and the Gingham Dog/Princess Dorothy and the Calico Cat, undated (Box 5)